carsontheweb.com 2013-06-11

# Privacy Policy - CarsOnTheWeb

CarsOnTheWeb will not sell or hire out any users’ personal data to third parties for marketing purposes. CarsOnTheWeb uses this information solely and exclusively in the manner described in this privacy policy. The privacy guidelines of this declaration apply to the services available under the domain and sub-domains of CarsOnTheWeb (the “website”) and are generally applicable to all CarsOnTheWeb websites under a Top Level Domain (TLD).

By registering and/or subscribing, the user acknowledges that he/she is bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. The Belgian law of 8 December 1992 on the protection of privacy gives all users the right to consult and correct their personal data. Pursuant to a special request by the user to this end, all his/her data will be removed from the CarsOnTheWeb databases.

As soon as a user registers and supplies us with his/her personal data, he/she is no longer anonymous for us. If he/she wishes to use our services, we may ask him/her to provide us with contact and identification details, invoicing details and other personal data on the various forms spread over the website. Where possible, we indicate what fields compulsorily have to be filled in and what fields are optional. You always have the possibility of not supplying certain information if you opt not to use a particular service or function.

Under certain circumstances we may ask for some additional financial data, such as, although not limited to: financial data and other data needed to invoice you for your use of our services.

All registered users of our services implicitly agree to the receipt of newsletters and updates from CarsOnTheWeb. Every user may at any time opt no longer to form part of our mailing list by adjusting his or her own mail settings online or sending a message to: [info@carsontheweb.com](mailto:info@carsontheweb.com).

We automatically trace certain information on the basis of your behaviour on the website(s). We use this information for internal research into the demographic data of our users and their interests and behaviour, in order to gain a better understanding of our users and to be able to provide them with a better service. When a user chooses to bid and buy on the website, we collect data on his/her bidding and buying behaviour. 

Sources of images on the website include: © Sam - Fotolia.com, © Erhan Ergin - Fotolia.com
